<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Magno Tairone on Magno Tairone</title>
    <link>https://magnotairone.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Magno Tairone on Magno Tairone</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2017 23:00:00 -0300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Geojags</title>
      <link>https://magnotairone.github.io/project/geojags/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jan 2019 11:32:14 -0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://magnotairone.github.io/project/geojags/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Bayesian hierarchical modeling for spatial data is challenging for professionals from other areas than statistics.
From a technical perspective, setting the model and the prior distributions are the simplest part of the process.
What makes it difficult is the computation of the posterior full conditionals and the implementation of the Gibbs Sampler algorithm.
The \texttt{BUGS} (Bayesian inference Using Gibbs Sampling) family of statistical softwares reduces the effort of modeling, since the user must indicate only the prior distributions and the likelihood function.
However, in general these softwares do not implement several spatial models, although users of \texttt{WinBUGS} and \texttt{OpenBUGS} can enjoy from the spatial add-on called \texttt{GeoBUGS}.
\texttt{JAGS} (Just Another Gibbs Sampler), the open-source \texttt{C++} developed version of the \texttt{BUGS} family, does not contain any function or distribution for spatial modeling.
This project aims to fill this gap through the implementation of an extension to the \texttt{JAGS} software, allowing users from different fields to perform a spatial data modeling and analysis.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Veraz</title>
      <link>https://magnotairone.github.io/project/stats4good/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jan 2019 01:52:28 -0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://magnotairone.github.io/project/stats4good/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
