<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Magno Tairone</title>
    <link>https://magnotairone.github.io/project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Magno Tairone</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Jan 2019 12:19:45 -0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://magnotairone.github.io/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Visualizing the inequalities in Brazil through the results of ENEM</title>
      <link>https://magnotairone.github.io/project/enem/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jan 2019 12:19:45 -0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://magnotairone.github.io/project/enem/</guid>
      <description>Brazil is known for its iniquality in several aspects, such as in income, education, race, ethnicity, gender, age, among others. With that in mind, we want to investigate whether this social inequality is reflected in the results of the ENEM exam.
Exame Nacional do Ensino Médio (ENEM) is a non-mandatory, standardized Brazilian national exam, which evaluates high school students in Brazil. The ENEM is the most important exam of its kind in Brazil, with more than 8.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Geojags</title>
      <link>https://magnotairone.github.io/project/geojags/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jan 2019 11:32:14 -0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://magnotairone.github.io/project/geojags/</guid>
      <description>Bayesian hierarchical modeling for spatial data is challenging for professionals from other areas than statistics. From a technical perspective, setting the model and the prior distributions are the simplest part of the process. What makes it difficult is the computation of the posterior full conditionals and the implementation of the Gibbs Sampler algorithm. The BUGS (Bayesian inference Using Gibbs Sampling) family of statistical softwares reduces the effort of modeling, since the user must indicate only the prior distributions and the likelihood function.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Veraz</title>
      <link>https://magnotairone.github.io/project/stats4good/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jan 2019 01:52:28 -0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://magnotairone.github.io/project/stats4good/</guid>
      <description>Veraz is a project of the Stats4good group, which is as team of graduate students that analyze data from the Brazilian federal government expenses. This is challenging since we deal with a great amout of data. We maintain a blog with our analyses.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>